- Pearson's Correlation
- Spearman's rho
- Bimodal Probability Distributions
- Plotting Equation for Gaussian Percentiles
- chi-squared distribution If you square a normal random variable, the result is a chi-squared random variable.
- Cornish-Fisher expansion A formula for approximating quintiles of a random variable based only on its first few cumulants.
- expected value A parameter describing the "center of gravity" of a distribution.
- joint normal distribution A multivariate distribution with normal marginal distributions.
- kurtosis A parameter describing the peakedness and tails of a distribution.
- lognormal distribution A random variable is lognormal if its logarithm is normal.
- normal distribution A continuous probability distribution whose probability density function has a "bell" shape.
- quantile A notion from probability that can be used as a parameter.
- standard deviation A parameter describing the dispersion of a distribution.
- uniform distribution A continuous probability distribution that has constant probability on a finite interval.
- tests for normality such as the Shapiro-Wilk or Kolmogorov-Smirnov test (not provided by Excel). 
- Fourier Analysis
- Poisson distribution 
- ANOVA - single factor, 2-factor
- R-squared, r2: =RSQ(known_y's, known_x's)
- Monte Carlo Simulation (Deterministic Model & Stochastic Model)
- QUARTILE, Median. Mode, 
- multivariate methods -- Correspondence Analysis, factor analysis, multidimensional scaling, and cluster analysis. 


	http://www.statisticalforecasting.com/forecasting-methods-menu.php
	Sales Forecasting
	Budget Forecasting
	How to Do Forecasting by Regression Analysis
	Box-Jenkins Methodology
	Modeling Financial Time Series
	BoxPlot
	Sales Forecasting Techniques
	Characteristics and Differences of Mode, Median and Mean
	More information on Forecasting
	Data Mining and Knowledge Discovery













